It all began here
Krampus Origins is a horror film directed by Joseph Mbah.
The first World War rages on when a group of American soldiers find a
mysterious artifact that can summon the ancient evil of the Krampus.
After the men are killed in action, the artifact is sent to the commanding
officer's widow who is a teacher at a small-town orphanage.
The orphans accidentally summon the Krampus and the teacher, and
her pupils are forced to battle this ancient evil.
Sister Rafus, played by Maria Olsen.
Adelia, played by Anna Harr.
Josephine, played by Katie Peabody.
Henrietta, played by Amelia Haberman.
Lena, played by Shannyn Hall.
Bram, played by Luke Waxman.
The Krampus (German: [ˈkʁampʊs]) is a horned anthropomorphic figure who, in the Central and Eastern Alpine folkloric tradition, is said to accompany
Saint Nicholas on visits to children during the night of 5 December (Krampusnacht; "Krampus Night"), immediately before the Feast of St.
Nicholas on 6 December.
In this tradition, Saint Nicholas rewards well-behaved children with small
gifts, while Krampus punishes badly behaved ones with birch rods.
The origin of the figure is unclear; some folklorists and anthropologists have postulated that it may have pre-Christian
origins, although historians generally consider this unlikely, as it is not attested until the 16th century.
In certain traditional parades and in such events as the Krampuslauf ("Krampus run"), some
young men dressed as Krampus attempt to scare the audience with their antics.
Krampus is featured on holiday greeting cards called Krampuskarten.
The figure has been imported into popular culture around the world,
and has appeared in movies, TV shows and video games.
The tone is dark.